<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
  <MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>4.0</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>Hand-crafted</MASTER_PAD_EDITOR>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description for Fill That PDF! PRO</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
  </MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>

  <Company_Info>
    <Company_Name>FillThatPDF!</Company_Name>
    <Address_1></Address_1>
    <City_Town></City_Town>
    <State_Province></State_Province>
    <Zip_Postal_Code></Zip_Postal_Code>
    <Country>United States</Country>
    <Company_WebSite_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com</Company_WebSite_URL>
    <Contact_Info>
      <Author_First_Name>Alex</Author_First_Name>
      <Author_Last_Name>Gordon</Author_Last_Name>
      <Author_Email>alexthebritgordon@gmail.com</Author_Email>
      <Contact_First_Name>Alex</Contact_First_Name>
      <Contact_Last_Name>Gordon</Contact_Last_Name>
      <Contact_Email>alexthebritgordon@gmail.com</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
    <Support_Info>
      <Sales_Email>alexthebritgordon@gmail.com</Sales_Email>
      <Support_Email>alexthebritgordon@gmail.com</Support_Email>
      <General_Email>alexthebritgordon@gmail.com</General_Email>
    </Support_Info>
  </Company_Info>

  <Program_Info>
    <Program_Name>Fill That PDF! PRO</Program_Name>
    <Program_Version>1.0.0</Program_Version>
    <Program_Release_Month>03</Program_Release_Month>
    <Program_Release_Day>02</Program_Release_Day>
    <Program_Release_Year>2026</Program_Release_Year>
    <Program_Cost_Dollars>99.99</Program_Cost_Dollars>
    <Program_Cost_Other_Code>USD</Program_Cost_Other_Code>
    <Program_Type>Commercialware</Program_Type>
    <Program_Release_Status>Major Release</Program_Release_Status>
    <Program_OS_Support>Mac OS X</Program_OS_Support>
    <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
    <Program_Change_Info>Version 1.0.0 - Initial Release</Program_Change_Info>
    <Program_System_Requirements>macOS 10.12 or later, Intel or Apple Silicon Mac, 700 MB disk space</Program_System_Requirements>
    <Program_Category>Business</Program_Category>
    <File_Info>
      <Filename_Versioned>FillThatPDF_PRO_v1.0.0.dmg</Filename_Versioned>
      <File_Size_Bytes>732075816</File_Size_Bytes>
      <File_Size_K>714917</File_Size_K>
      <File_Size_MB>698.0</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
    <Expire_Info>
      <Expire_Count>0</Expire_Count>
      <Expire_Based_On>Never</Expire_Based_On>
      <Expire_Other_Info>License does not expire</Expire_Other_Info>
    </Expire_Info>
  </Program_Info>

  <Program_Descriptions>
    <English>
      <Char_Desc_45>Advanced fillable PDF creator with editor</Char_Desc_45>
      <Char_Desc_80>Create fillable PDFs with visual field editor, AI assistant, and bulk processing</Char_Desc_80>
      <Char_Desc_250>Fill That PDF! PRO is the complete PDF form creation suite. It includes everything in the Standard version plus a visual field editor for precise control over every field, an AI assistant powered by Google Gemini, unlimited bulk processing, conditional rules, and calculated fields.</Char_Desc_250>
      <Char_Desc_450>Fill That PDF! PRO is the complete professional PDF form creation suite for macOS. Beyond automatic field detection, it includes a full visual field editor where you can drag, resize, rename, and style every form field with pixel-perfect precision. Set up calculated fields with formulas, create conditional visibility rules, and use the built-in AI assistant to speed up your workflow. PRO supports unlimited bulk processing and advanced formatting options including custom validation, JavaScript actions, and multi-page form editing.</Char_Desc_450>
      <Char_Desc_2000>Fill That PDF! PRO is the complete professional PDF form creation suite for macOS, designed for power users who need full control over their fillable PDF forms.

Building on the intelligent automatic detection engine, Fill That PDF! PRO adds a comprehensive visual field editor that gives you precise control over every aspect of your form fields. Drag, resize, align, and style fields directly on the PDF canvas with real-time preview.

PRO-exclusive features include:
- Visual Field Editor with drag-and-drop field placement, resizing, and alignment tools
- Calculated Fields supporting sum, average, min, max, product, and count operations across multiple source fields
- Conditional Rules engine for show/hide logic based on field values
- AI Assistant powered by Google Gemini for intelligent field suggestions and workflow automation
- Unlimited Bulk Processing to convert entire folders of PDFs in one operation
- Advanced field properties including character limits, comb fields, password masking, visibility controls, rotation, default values, and custom validation rules
- Custom JavaScript actions for mouse, focus, and blur events
- Lasso/marquee selection for batch field operations
- Field formatting with date, phone, ZIP code, currency, and number masks
- Per-field font, color, border, and alignment customization

All Standard features are also included:
- Automatic field detection for text fields, checkboxes, radio buttons, and dropdowns
- Smart field naming based on nearby labels
- Test fill mode with sample data
- Customizable global settings for field appearance
- Standards-compliant output compatible with Adobe Acrobat, Preview, and all major PDF viewers

Fill That PDF! PRO runs natively on both Intel and Apple Silicon Macs as a universal application with a bundled Python engine requiring no additional software installation.

The ultimate tool for businesses, form designers, and anyone who needs professional fillable PDF creation with complete control.</Char_Desc_2000>
      <Keywords>pdf, fillable pdf, form fields, pdf forms, pdf editor, visual editor, form creator, calculated fields, conditional rules, ai assistant, bulk processing, checkbox, radio button, dropdown, mac pdf, pdf tool</Keywords>
    </English>
  </Program_Descriptions>

  <Web_Info>
    <Application_URLs>
      <Application_Info_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com</Application_Info_URL>
      <Application_Order_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com</Application_Order_URL>
      <Application_Screenshot_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com/screenshot.png</Application_Screenshot_URL>
      <Application_Icon_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com/icon.png</Application_Icon_URL>
      <Application_XML_File_URL>https://fillthatpdf.com/pad_pro.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
    <Download_URLs>
      <Primary_Download_URL>https://github.com/FillThatPDF/FillThatPDF-releases-pro/releases/download/v1.0.0/FillThatPDF_PRO_v1.0.0.dmg</Primary_Download_URL>
    </Download_URLs>
  </Web_Info>

  <Permissions>
    <Distribution_Permissions>This software may not be redistributed without written permission from FillThatPDF!</Distribution_Permissions>
    <Copyright_Holder>FillThatPDF!</Copyright_Holder>
    <Copyright_Year>2026</Copyright_Year>
  </Permissions>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
